A Guide to the General Records of Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society, Virginia Chapter, 1924-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
General Records of Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society, Virginia Chapter, 1924-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-24/23/1.911
This collection consists of ca. 2.7 shelf feet (ca. 1500 items).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1991 July 11.
Scope and Content Information
General records of the University of Virginia Chapter of Sigma Xi, the scientific research society, chiefly correspondence but including anniversary awards, membership lists, and minutes.
Contents List
- Group I
  - [Correspondence] 1959-1967, 9 folders (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence] 1968-[1979], 11 folders (Box 2)
  - [Correspondence] 1979-1985, 6 folders (Box 3)
  - [Correspondence] 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 4)
- Group II
  - Allan Talbott Gwathmey Award 1971-1974 (Box 4)
  - Annual Meeting 1977 (Box 4)
  - Annual Meeting 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Anniversary Awards 1977 (Box 4)
  - Anniversary Awards 1978 (Box 4)
  - Anniversary Awards 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Anniversary Awards Submissions 1981 (Box 4)
  - [Associate Member Certificates] 1984 (Box 4)
  - Associate Members 1978 (Box 4)
  - Certificates n.d. (Box 4)
  - Full Members 1978 (Box 4)
  - Local History Of n.d. (Box 5)
  - Mailing List 1977 (Box 5)
  - Mailing Lists 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Manual and Handbook 1979, n.d. (Box 5)
  - National Meeting 1980 (Box 5)
  - New Members 1981 (Box 5)
  - New Full and Associate Members 1979 (Box 5)
  - Nomination for Membership 1977-[1978] (Box 5)
  - Nominees 1980 (Box 5)
  - Nominees 1982 (Box 6)
  - Nominees 1983 (Box 6)
  - Nominees 1984 (Box 6)
  - Nominees Who Did Not Respond 1981 (Box 6)
  - President and Visitors' Research Prize 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - President and Visitors' Research Prize 1979 (Box 6)
  - President and Visitors' Research Prize 1982 (Box 6)
  - President's File (G.M. Hornberger) 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Records 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Stationary and Form Letters n.d. (Box 6)
  - Treasurer's Report 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Book of Dues 1961-1967 (Box 6)
  - Signatures of Members & Associates Under the Constitution and Bylaws 1924-1982 (Box 7)
  - Treasurer's Book 1933-1961 (Box 7)
  - Minutes of the Virginia Chapter, Sigma Xi 1951-1967 (Box 7)
  - Membership 3x5 cards n.d. (Othertype Card File Tray #70)